[BIRDS CHIRPING]
♪♪♪
♪ I SAW THE SIGN OR AN OMEN ♪
♪ ON THE BRANCHES, IN THE MORNING ♪
♪ IT WAS RIGHT AFTER I ♪
♪ LOST A FRIEND WITHOUT WARNING ♪
♪ WORDS UNSAID ♪
♪ SCARLET-RED ♪
♪ CARDINAL ♪
♪ ARE YOU BRINGING ME A MESSAGE FROM THE OTHER SIDE? ♪
♪ ARE YOU TELLIN' ME I'M ON SOMEBODY'S MIND? ♪
♪ DON'T LEAVE ME BEHIND ♪
♪ I TOOK A WALK IN THE CITY ♪
♪ TO CLEAR MY HEAD FOR A MOMENT ♪
♪ TURNED MY COLLAR TO THE WIND ♪
♪ ON THE STREET, IT WAS BLOWIN' ♪
♪ AND THERE HE WAS ♪
♪ ABOVE MY HEAD ♪
♪ CARDINAL ♪
♪ ARE YOU BRINGING ME A MESSAGE FROM THE OTHER SIDE? ♪
♪ ARE YOU TELLIN' ME I'M ON SOMEBODY'S MIND? ♪
♪ DON'T LEAVE ME BEHIND ♪
♪♪♪
♪ ARE YOU JUST WATCHING AND WAITING FOR SPRING? ♪
♪ DO YOU HAVE SOME KIND OF MAGIC TO BRING? (PRETTY BIRD) ♪
♪ DO YOU HAVE SOME KIND OF MAGIC? ♪
♪ CARDINAL ♪
♪ ARE YOU BRINGING ME A MESSAGE FROM THE OTHER SIDE? ♪
♪ ARE YOU TELLIN' ME I'M ON SOMEBODY'S MIND? ♪
♪ CARDINAL ♪
♪ ARE YOU BRINGING ME A MESSAGE FROM THE OTHER SIDE? ♪
♪ ARE YOU TELLIN' ME I'M ON SOMEBODY'S MIND? ♪
♪ CARDINAL ♪
[BIRDS CHIRPING]